Any resemblance to real persons, living or dead. Is purely
Smoking and Alcohol Consumption are injurious to health.
P.A COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING
Y L/
INEWSI 24x7
'ULUVAS ETWORK EWS
uuuuuuuuuuuuuu
TING
EWS
CTING
NEWS 24x7
'ULUVAS ETWORK EWS
Tech Darshi PACE MEMES
Proud to be a Mangalorcan
Mangaloreans JUST GAMATH Beauty of Tulunadu Namma Uchila
Tulunadu(Official)
Mangaloreans
Tech Darshi
JUST GAMATH
Proud to be a Mangalorcan
PACE MEMES
Namma Uchila
Tech Darshi PACE MEMES
Tulunadu(Official)
Proud to be a Mangalorcan
Namma Uchila
JUST GAMATH
Tech Darshi PACE MEMES
Tulunadu(Official) Proud to be a Mangalorean
Mangaloreans
Mangaloreans JUST GAMATH Beauty of Tulunadu Namma Uchila
Tulunadu(Official) Proud to be a
Mangaloreans
4 Beauty of Tulunadu
Namma Uchila
Mangaloreans JUST GAMATH
Tech Darshi PACE MEMES
Proud to be a
Mangaloreans JUST GAMATH Beauty of Tulunadu Namma Uchila
PACE MEMES
Tulunadu( Proud to be a Mangalorean
Mangaloreans JUST GAMATH Beauty of Namma Uchila
Proud to be a
Mangaloreans JUST GAMATH Beauty ot Uchila
JUST Beauty
1o bé &
Mangaloreans Ushila
.
)
2 h (43
A 1TULU FILM
A FILM
& Tech,friednship & life
YV AN
VIKAS K PRAJWAL BHAT ARUN MB
S AN
SAHIL RAI
"l am not the one who d
its you..
£S NFE TAK
!'FE TAKES A TURN
4 .
-
WHERE LIFE TAKES A TURN
"You have done a mistake, didn't you? " A
" natural when you go wrong
-
" natural consequences when you go wron
"
" you go
" i3 matural o
gfare you??!!! "
" Im already tensed, please leave me
lone "
LY
A
N
" to give the solution "
is that?! "
¢
" Once upon a time even I've been through this
Za
77 r story?? hat's you " Oh!! w
" Its not just a story , Its a bitter reality of my life "
Za
" then listen... It all began with a kabbaddi match with our old rivals... "
"Suresh, A simple person
my close friend "
SORESH:
"Suresh, A simple person so .called m¥ close friend "
4 I  ) - I
iend, Preethum is his ATM "
Akash, Preethu
‘ .
is his ATM "
" Akash, mo
I
) " Akash, Preethum is his ATM "
" Akash, Preethum's friend, morelike Preethum is his ATM "
" Every gang should have an item , in our'ss that is Arun AKA manmohan singh..
should a our'ss that is Arun AKA manmoh
S - he is the only day dreams,inside the opposition court forgetting to tell kabbaddi "
YD sition
he is the only one who day dreams inside the opposition court forgetting to tell kabbaddi "
A
H
"(Refree) Rider "
v
SUDEESH
"When is your entry?"
" match finisher al
s at the end "
.   & J y 1
" the team coudn't digest their defeat, they showd their anger on Arun,
do you thik we will just sit and watch if they touch our "
L.
st he haave Id've caught all in one "
4 If got a ride, W
/
—  « A
If had
uId all in one "
he haave done! ) If i had got a ride, I would've caught all in one "
" whatbest he haave done' If i had got , would ve in one "
he haave donel
If i had got a ride, would ve al
them in one "
had got a rlde, l would them In one
)  rﬁatdh head
AN
"l don't
smce suaeesh crawled in e won"
l - ‘ " / rawled /
esterday, since sudeesh cr Ly v A 4
" Y
)
y Arun Yesterday, smce Irf gra - "  AL A
!
I
yea mahn , give it for sure, how many i shoul tell you... "
mahn , i'll for sure, how many ti shoul
mahn , for sure shoul b4 -
mahn i'll givesit for sure, i shoul 1 V4 Y :
21 ho was that? need money?
A
why are you worrying for that when i am there, take as as you need... "
-
We went on trips whenever we were free. We used to have loads of fun.
We picked on each one of our group members indefinitely.
! I
/ ,
. . its tail! Isn't it different? Doesn't it
' it different? Doesn't it a belt?"
it different Doesn't it resemble
-
o
II N - it different Doesn't it
- . lat it Doesn't it -
it a
N  A  I I II I   I I  B . its tail! it different? Doesn't it resemb belt? N
I'll deposit the neces
4 mount in your account. Go ahead, ‘
mount in your a
ccount.
N
N 4 "Thanks a lot, dad. Love
f I "Thanks a dad. ie you""
/
—
fayyyy" lphiii
"Yayyyy!! I'm getting an iph , Akash!!"
f yyyyl' Im gettmg an iphones, -
anI Aka§ g g
gettlng an iphones, Aka§
yyyy" ge’ttlng Iphone5, Aké§
YY yll I iph 3 A
I'm getting an iphones, Akash!!"
"
P
YYYY" I'm an iphon 3
l .ﬂ need treat."
-
I I need treat."
"Just t? Keep gift from me!!" ‘
? Keep this cell as a gift from I
- )
Just treat? Keep this cell as a gift from me!!"
get a new cell phone I I
"Hey guys,
"Hey guys, Preethu gonna get a new cell pho
é
N
"Hey guys, a get a ceII pho
»
a get.a new 24
is gonna new
‘  g o hat calls for a party."
Y
"Oh! You somehow et a free cell phone!!!"
4 I
"Oh! You somehow mana t a free cell phone!!!"
-
"Let's .ea
IIIIm gu el s
guessing h IIIIm
was just kidding, What sh
3 .
"l was just kidding, right? What I do if .6.‘
"I feel you apologize to him."
"I feel you must apologize to him."
-
"Some don't like being laughed at. So, I decided to apologize to him."
2 '
"Apparently, you've a girlfriend I
ly, you've a girlfriend r
"Appare
Sh an angel from heaven
"Hey Sudeesh, come here... She hmm.. She is A ,
"I gotta leave. Got some work to tend to. Bye. Bye Akash." .
ye Akash.
© ©
L
Got some wor
" Everything was fine and we were all together but....
l
-y
(Suresh on call)
-
"A Manmohan... "
Akash:"Who is that??"
-
" It's an important call."
A '
"Tell man, who's that?"
"Why are you supporting him?? Is he your cousin bro?? "
"Why did you It's Preetham's money
terested
/
T
did you hit ham's money
I rested in!!"
"Why did vy, money you're interested in!!" I  I
did tham's money interested I  I
did you'
IIIS mone Ule llltele ted
"Why did you hit him??
Preetham's money you're interested in!!"
"Why hit him??
money you're interested
hat did you just say? IIW
"What did you just say????"
(Total silence following the fight)
"There was a time when we were more than ready to give up our life for friendship
.
- -
but now here we are fighting against each other."
5 N I & I
after two weeks
"Hello daddy."
"Why do you sound worried dad?"
"Hmmm.. Tell me!"
™
n
"Hello?"
"Hmm.. Go on."
"Nothing dad.
You had said me you'll get me a new
Will I get it within this wee
The kind of things you've been up to, you deserve 4
?f "I know everything about you "Get studying. Score well.
‘ I "Hello? Dad?
- a
"Look at her figure bro! Yeah.. An amazing figure."
time if I se her, I'll break your
"Next time I
fating her, I'll break 1
"Next time if I se her, I'll break yourb/
"The situation had totally reversed. I had no idea as to what had happened to my dad.
lv
give me whenever I asked him, doesn
Earlier on, he used to give me whenever I asked him, he
!
"‘
3 had asked for a bike and reed to buy me one but when I calledhim up yesterday he denie
d to buy ay he denied.
' or a bike and he agreed to buy 4 edhim up yesterday he denied. l
id that he won't even give me a penny. happened, buddy." /
was SItuatlon O
' N
was awes
1I ife was awesome I 5ItuatIon
1 wa S awe eso
: //’ was awesome but no
4 &
- 4 / was awesome:but now I'm’ /
. ¢
A '.
was now
/ Y
y me. I dont know who is it!"
-
ne. I dont know who is it!" 5 . -
laying up with me."
- - -
)
"I never thbught you'd turn out this bad."
.
h I er thought you'd turn out this 2
g
" I hate you! Dont call me Good bye!"
" I hate you! Dont call me ever again! Good bye!"
/‘
--/:" i  /
(New Reqeved)
-y
—
"What the hell is this?? Just take a look at this... "
™
the hell
3 ¥
"We were msepara then. Look at us now."
n ‘   4  - "We were Look at us now."
R
"We were then
N - : / "Everyone went on own way, what do we do?"
went on t
&y
I"I way, What do we do?"
lly ari
tota
- I received a call from my friend Suresh. I hoped for a new beginning of our destroyed frlendshlp,
¢
4 just like the old times and set out meet him...
"Everything happened because of you. You are the sole reason. You destroyed my life. Tell him Akash!"
— "Everythlng happened becar — he sole reason. You destroye my-llfe . Tell hlm
-
"Everythlng ée o‘f‘
- 1 the sole reason. destroyed myhfe 'FeII hlm
- are the sole reason. hlm Akash'
happened.
"Everything
e of he sole reason. destroyed my life. Tell Kka§h"
the ma
. I B I —
I
in reason which destroyed our
ason deStI‘O ed OU II dS I” Y I III hl hl p
)  -   I I I -
thing started because of me.. I should "There is a solution for this... " . -
-
I
A
to know
-
t his mls‘takes.
I Akashs
— A, 7
mi’stakes s
'
- 7 A
t his mrstakes
Al s
y I received gall.
'  I . to  I
»
's -‘
. mrstakes i
Al Akash
A wee 3
1 -
t his mistakes.
A Akash
¢ -
A
I
l - recewed ,Akash -
r .," : X
N
‘
was Akas
up."
.
b€
And this I hoped that everything will be normal
again since it was Akash who called ui’ 3 I
A I' "Look guys, Manmeha peaking
In a will de nltel im rove'"" dl
er rig
you all got to  Cheers!! Drink the coffee
:  Finallyy all got toge  Cheers!! Drink the
'.
" Prajwal: Finally, you all got together right? Cheers!! Drink the coffee."
I ' - N 3 coffee) They forgot to eten the
-
- ‘ (spits coffee) They forgot to eten the coffee." : ‘ '
- ll S
- ’l
- 3
. coffee) They forgot to 3
I . .
A . "The story that continues has the same bitter twist.."
you done to my ded your Anjali!"
you done to my Anjali?? vided your Anjali!"
"Hello! Anjali? esh, I have to say you something.."
"There is a solution for this......
) , .-
- - ‘"No aII of us have to go
"You fell???!!! happehed to
‘ht:-f
" -
"You
f : I
- ?
"You Nothing happened to -  )
Preethum and Akash informed Suresh and Arun that I slipped near the falls and was swept by the water and they were helpless.
Suresh felt numb"'as though all hIs wa drained out of hlm dsnt even move for a
hIs drained out of hlm even move
though all his energy drained hIm eyen move for a while.
A , Suresh felt though all hIS ener drained dmt move fr a whIIe
drained him,
A
dint eve.n move while:
num though hIs drained hIm dmt eve.n move fer-a
Suresh felt though hIs energy ’w drained out’of dint while:
Suresh felt pugh all his energy dralned hIm dfnt a while: 1
- Suresh felt numb out him
ren for & while.
energy was
for &
as the of him. He
energy was ove for & while.
Suresh numb, as though energy was drained out of He dint even move for a
Surash felt numb, as though all his energy wes drained of He dint even move for a
numb, as
drained out of He dint
Surash
drainad of
ENErgy was
Surash
of
Surash EHH e
I
I out of him
m
Suresh felt numb, as tho all his energy was drained out of him. He din 'e for a while.
Suresh felt
drained out of him. He dint -
Suresh felt numb, as though all his energy was drained out of him. He dint even move for a while.
for a while.
Suresh felt numb, as of him. He dint
felt numb, as out of him. He dint while:
h felt numb, as
wes &
move for & while.
After spot where I was last Maybe waiting for some to happen so that he‘ me again. d v
at the spot Where I was ast Maybe waiting for some miracle to happen so that he co did happen.. - y -
After a!tl
Maybe som happen SO that he couI see And happen.. )
Maybe waltlng for some miracle to that he coul
see me again. And happen ‘
d Maybe waiting for .that he coul see And happen
I wes seen. fhat he
spot where I see he could heppen..
Aftar sometime he 2 £ Mayba for again. f
so he could
where last see
After sometime he at Mayba soma 522 And
where I "5 so
s he could
he at where I was so fha 522 Me again. Anc did happen..
t where I seen. he could
he at
me again. And f
so he could
t where I was
T
so he
‘
’
was ceen. o
ppen so that he did - -
After sometime h  Maybe waiting see me
’///
After Maybe waiting for
again:
he arfivad at I wes last seen. Mayba for happen so that he could
me again. And that did
But this time there was an eye witness....
Preethum and Akash were unaware of it. Preethum lied again saying that Suresh slipped in to the falls as Sudeesh due to the shock he suffered from Sudeesh's death.
rything dint utter a sy ight time. He feared fo
syllable fearing it may
dear
fearing it may
his own dear
rything dint utter a syllable fearing it may for his own dear
fearing it may his own dear life
llable
fearing it may ht time. He feared for his own dear lif
A N
fearing it may his own dear life
But something strange and unexpected happened...
OW d ? : : H II ld AkaSh dle
“How d id Akash dle"?"’“
How dld Akash dIe7777
.-/
"There are many things in which are unexplained."
death of Akash, that there was something place and unlike the last time,
petrified:
d Arun were petrified.
wrong about this
the unusual death of Akash, Preethumiand Arun were petrified. d that there was something wrong about this place and unlike the last time,
After the unusual death of Akash, Preethum and Arun were petrified. Arun believed that there was something really wrong about this place and unlike the last time,
the second time it happened he revealed what he had witnessed before and suggested Preethum to surrender finally.
But Preethum hated his suggestion. He felt insecure wondering Arun might end up confessing the truth to the police.
But Preebhum hatec He felt insecure mught end up confessmg police.
‘rut- the ‘po
Hesfelt
gestion.
end
/But
AN
suggestlon
t end
Preethum hated his suggestion. He insecure ht end up confessing -
Arunmight end
confessing the police. 3
astion. ht end up
He felt insecure wondering Arun m confessmg thé
He felt insecure wo dérlng Arun might end up
confessmg
wondermg Arun mlght end up
' -
felt wondermg
( confessmg e police.
e truth
He felt truth
confessing
g confessing th
The very thing Arun had e finally happened.
- - -
- . I  o A
3 N . . "Two innocent lives were wake of
— I  - — Z
"What is the moral of t
The.innocents th helnous survive."
"LIfe - ) die but helnous their exnstenc.
N
"LIfe
-
"LIfe isnt fair.
die but thelr very eXIstenc.
-
- ! : . 5 isnt Innocents die but heinous live regretting very existence."
isnt fair—
regretting their very I
ample?"
ygu
I
ave made a mistake already. y dont you make a new beginning forgetting the past?!"
So, w
-
"What do you .mean?"
“Friendship is the purest form of relationship.
Dont ruin it."
-
Dont rum it."
"Friendship is the pures
Dont ruin it." A
"Friendship is  Dont ruin it."
S
e
)
may hav to tell your story sitti
"Innocents die but heinous live. they will live regretting their ve
existance"
/l . - -
It is true but
"Alright, it's time I leave to my place, goodbye!!"
4 o W  / - -
-
I - Pl'a... r
"Who was I talking to all this time?"
P
“I'm sorry."
"I knew that you'll come to know about your mistake"
"There is no graet punishment than regretting"
"Time is beyond anyone's control and changes constantly.."
"Time bayond
contrel and changes
bayond am
.   we expect fr6m Ilfe
opposite happens: AIways
"God alone decides a person's life span."
kes God punishes them."
"There is an end for each and everything."
"U had asked for my place?!??
It's Charmadi." (Smirks.)
Casting Sudeesh Naik Preetham Akash
Suresh
Sudeesh Naik Preetham Akash Arun MB
Akash Arun MB Vranda G Rao Praiwal Bhat
Arun MB Vranda G Rao Prajwal Bhat Vikas K Rahul Rao
Vranda G Rao Prajwal Bhat Vikas K Rahul Rao Sandeep NJ
Vikas K Rahul Rao Sandeep NJ Monish B Kalmadi Manjunath
Manjunath Vinod
vinoa
b 4.4
Thanke ¢
Special Thanks to Kiran Kumar Prashanth Poojary Uchila
Anudeep Kumar Padil
Prashanth Poojary Uchila Anudeep Kumar Padil Dinesh K Suvarna
Pravith Kundar
UUJDII Anudeep Kumar Padil Dinesh K Suvarna Pravith Kundar
Madhu Kumar
Dinesh K Suvarna Pravith Kundar Madhu Kumar
Shreyas
§
Pravith Kundar Madhu Kumar Shreyas
Rohan Mendonca
Madhu Kumar Shreyas Rohan Mendonca
Sharath Shettigar
Shreyas Rohan Mendonca Sharath Shettigar
Sandeep Kumar
Rohan Mendonca Sharath Shettigar Sandeep Kumar
Sukesh Bolar
Sharath Shettigar Sandeep Kumar Sukesh Bolar
Peter Rodrigous
Sandeep Kumar Sukesh Bolar Peter Rodrigous
Shruthi Kumari
Sukesh Bolar Peter Rodrigous Shruthi Kumari Vranda G Rao
Shruthi Kumari Vranda G Rao Sudeesh Naik Akash Bangera
AL
Vranda G Rao Sudeesh Naik Akash Bangera
Preetham
Sudeesh Naik Akash Bangera Preetham
Suresh M
W
AKash bangera Preetham Suresh M Arun MB
« I
- Preetham Suresh M Arun MB Sandeep NJ
Suresh M Arun MB Sandeep NJ Monish B Kalmadi
Arun MB Sandeep NJ Monish B Kalmadi Vinod
I I
UGIIUUG'J Monish B Kalmadi Vinod Manjunath
Rahul Rao
Manjunath Rahul Rao Richard Rathan Shettigar
Rahul Rao Richard Rathan Shettigar Sahil Rai
Rathan Shettigar Sahil Rai Shobhith Raj
Sooraj H
Sahil Rai Shobhith Raj Sooraj H U Chandrashekhar Bhat
Shobhith Raj Sooraj H U Chandrashekhar Bhat
Vishwanath B
£
11 U Chandrashekhar Bhat Vishwanath B Kamalakshi
Premaleela Bhat
Vishwanath B Kamalakshi Premaleela Bhat
Prabhavathi
o Kamalakshi Premaleela Bhat Prabhavathi
Amar Shatty
Premaleela Bhat Prabhavathi Amar Shetty
Ranjith Suvarna
Prabhavathi Amar Shetty Ranjith Suvarna
And our beloved lecturers
peloved
¢
I Vikas K & Prajwal Bhat
& Bhat
K &