- ml
Shri. Dr. Mohan Alva, Alva’s Foundation Shri. Dr. Sudharam Rai, Global Hospital Shri. Rajeev Shetty, Hotel Palkhi Shri. Anil Shetty, Hotel Palkhi
Shri. Lawrence D'silva Shri. Rohan Das Electrical Point, Mangalore
Shri. K. K. Pejawar Ajay Sports Club ®, Kulai
Billawa Sangha Urwa ® Urwa Yuvaka Sangha ® Ashok Nagar Yuvak Sangha ® Hoigebail Friends
Shri. Komal & family, Balmatta Shri. Niranjan Salian, Balmatta
I I  I I
1 I I ! x
will do it Peter.
What will i get in return?
- a » "
I guarantee you can’t do it Bhaskar,
LEY
even if you have a lifetime.
Are you challenging me?
od I'l talk to her Peter. What will you give?
I I
Two plates of Banana Podi in Kudla Café.... kay?
Do you agree?
I
1 will offer you three plates.
2)
You better pay first. I don’t trust you.
Consider
You will surely lose the money.
Hear that?
No way, Raghu.
-
When will he speak? Her brother might kill him.
Let’s see.
-
Okay, see.
Si
She will be here soon.
What mischief are you boys upto today?
Quiet, Pandu uncle!
I
Go fry two plates of Banana Podi.
Oh man, she is coming, she is coming...
3 3 a May I borrow your accounts boo!
» Ws
I
You're not in college, right?
Then, why do you need my book?
I
I may need it for next year
L I feel, I might lose the bet today.
I A
/  Hey, that’s her brother right?
s her brother right?
Hey, that
. 1 What a fool Bhaskar is! He's done for.
x 1 »
First clear the exams,
then we'll see.
is screwed
How come you are here? How come?
Who is he?
Is he bothering you?
Book? Is this a place to ask for a book?
Why are you acti ng like a fool?
What are you looking at?
° 3  E
T
E 5
Nothing... But, I will never forget this day.
Q o  I
Bloody cheapsters!
g
1985 Under 19 Kabaddi Championship Final 1985 - 19
He is still not here!
1985 Under 19 Kabaddi Chal -19 3 2,803
Must be still asleep!
1985 Under 19 Kabaddi Ch: 1985 - 19 J 2,803
Is this a day to be late? Idiot!
Still sleeping? What are you saying?
He wouldn't have slept all night!
The 'Finals' would have kept him awake.
Bhaskar, do you know where he is?
Come on boys, focus, concentrate.
I am confident, he will surely come.
I I my son...after all, being called a 'Kabadi Player"...
But if you still want to go...
- i then forget about your parents.
You can sleep on the Kabadi gro
und itself.
J i We've worked hard to reach till here.
J
I promise I won't play anything ever again.
I am not stopping you.
Go! Go and play today as well.
But I will disown a dishonest son,
1 who lied to his father to play a silly game.
Ng
I am sorry for being
dishonest with you, Dad.
) A But if I would have told you the truth,
you have let me play at all.
/ a So, you played even after knowing I won't approve of it?
N
but I think you should come once...
S   5 a
3    3
you should see how well I play.
All the best for your match.
J
Why did you come now?
Don’t hit him.
Its done now. Leave it.
I I
I i Don’t show me your face!
I /
Raghu. I've a meeting with a supplier.
I'll see you at the office.
Oh, okay Dad.
Come soon dear, it's getting late.
Kabadi...Kabadi...hold your hands properly.
u
1 will pick you up in the afternoon after work.
Okay, Dad...Bye
I have asked to prepare Chickpea and Ivy Gourd curry.
have our lunch together. Okay.
Change your dress after practice.
If your grandfather comes to know I let you play kabadi,
I'll have to sleep outside with the dogs.
Okay...
Kabadi...Kabadi...Kabadi
Pooja, go change.
I ES -
Sir, your father had called
Dad, did you call me?
Why do you have a cell-phone?
I have been calling you,
but you are not receiving the call.
What's the point of having a cell-phone?
Then I called the shop, you hadn't reached there either.
I had asked you to contact a client...
Dad...I will call you back.
Raghu...How are you?
am good.
It's been a long time since we last spoke.
As far as i remember, we spoke last Diwali. Right?
I called you because...
sad news.
What happened, Peter?
Our Pandu uncle...
passed away this morning...
Were you there?
Gautham and I were there.
He passed peacefully.
:
© c
Today, evening.
I
Okay...then I will meet you there.
How did he pass?
Heart attack...
I
—
He had an attack before, too...
I
his heart was weak...
—
so this time he couldn't be saved.
I 4
— 4 x é
When is the funeral?
Today, evening.
I
y K
Okay. It's not necessary for me to come, right?
I —
J
I i
Dad...it would be good, if you could come...
I would've come...
i 2
J
)
but there is an urgent meeting with a showroom investor,
so it'll be difficult to attend.
AY I I
Asif, do you remember... used to take lot of beatings from him.
a
Yes, Kishore.
In childhood days, you got the 'highest' amount of beatings.
I
Even if your bones became powder,
you never felt bad.
I miss those days...
When my father passed away,
he gave me strength.
Sat through the whole night, talked to me.
He was really a great man, Peter.
each and every one of us needed him,
one way or another.
I
His good deeds can't be forgotten.
By the way,
did you meet Gautham?
y
Yes, I feel very sorry for him.
Now the kid has no one...
Why are you saying that?
wy
Good evening. How are you all?
Good. Good
.
Brother Pandu was a good human being,
at
So sad. I am very sorry.
I 7
I'm glad that you came.
Back in my playing days,
brother Pandu was the the only one I respected.
W
Playing days means,
you don't play anymo
I left the game 10 years ago.
Now I have started up a small business
I'll go pay my respects.
-
Listen, where is Bhaskar?
Is he ever going to show up?
’ »
in...
a 4 y is not my lucky day.
Now if police raids,
Oy, Oy...Give the money. Give the money.
f
re are you going without payi
First you invite, then you bite!
re is the remaining amount?
Why do you play if you don’t have money?
You took all my hard-earned money.
What do i give you now?
What nonsense man,
you didn't pay that day, too!
- 3
When we come, full respect, when our money gets over...no respect!
What a gambler!
I
When money gets over, no respect.
» il  A
Respect needs
a K)
I
I can't believe he's come drunk.
Everybody is here. How are you all?
A
3 I i
When is the funeral?
Just few more minutes
So, is the café closed today?
For the café to be closed for one day...
Pandu uncle had to die. Hah...
Hah...Hah
I
. If he were here, he would've lost it.
jo
"What if I am dead?"
"People are not hungry or what?"
"Why is the café closed?" Hah...hah...hah...
If he were here, he would've said that.
Did you call that
A
Is he going to come?
Mm-Hmm?
»
I called him, said he's on the way.
I doubt he'll come.
I've to see it to believe it.
How are you Bhaskar?
Kishore.
How are you Asif?
No worries, Raghu.
Seems like you're disappointed I came.
I'm going inside.
- A I
What man? I won't ask, you ask.
, Raghu.
Listen
Bhaskar and I were talking. And we thought...
We should drink tonight...
in Pandu Uncle's memory.
And it's been a while, right?
What do you say?
do one thing.
You go ahead,
I'm tried, going home.
What tired?
We've met after so long!
spoil the mood.
But not in his house. go to some hotel.
What is this? Am I a football?
IN
He won't come to your house, says lets go to a hotel.
I can’t come to a hotel.
WN
We get drunk in a hotel, don't watch what we say,
-
—
someone records us, uploads it on whatsapp - too many problems!
I won't come. Go ask him.
Raghu!
It’s been years we've met...
Can you let...
bygones be bygones?
Okay, I'll pick you up at 7 PM.
4 I 3
Yes? Thank you!
As »
He said he'll pick me up at 7 PM.
7 PM is too soon for me.
Ask him, if 8 PM is fine?
To Pandu Uncle in heaven, cheers!
So...
Bhaskar...where is your wife?
She's gone to her mother’s.
Her mother's sick...she's taken the kid as well.
A
Her mother's
Her mother's sick...she's taken
I
The jerk is not too bad...
Oh, work?
I
I've added two new buses this year.
Oh! So, total?
Totally, 17.
One more and he'll be Guru Swamy!
Yes, you'd love to touch my feet, right?
Now, I want to say something.
How about we go to Pandu uncle’s café for breakfast tomorrow?
I'll be there on time,
but ask this Father-fearing guy,
if his father will allow him?
Did I need this?
- 12
I'd told you, I didn't want to come!
K
I'm leaving. Good night.
Hey Raghu, wait. I'll come, too.
Yes, leave us like you left us that day.
You'll always do as your father says.
He loses it when he's drunk!
That's why I didn't want to come.
aL Your Idea is the best. talk at Kudla Café tomorrow.
I am leaving, good night.
£ Q 2 3
You can leave as well!
Pandu uncle, cheers!
»
I KUDLA CAFE
Look at is this Peter... Kudla Café is still the same!
Yes, Raghu. Nothing has changed.
I
Oh my god. Brother Jairam,
You are still here?
I
How are you?
Yes, still alive! What do you want now?
Didn’t you recognize me? It's me, Raghu?
So? As if you are Rajinikanth!
I A
I J
I have been working here for the past 40 years,
I
I have served tea, coffee for thousands of people.
How many people will I remember?
Just get me a tea, will you?
-
Also, I asked you to get one Bunce. What is this, is it a Bunce?
So what happened now?
J
This is fried in ail,
So let’s do one thing, I'll get you some sugar,
You eat this and sugar together,
I I
He is mad, still the same.
I
...no sugar in the buns...no salt in the sugar! My foot!
Whatever you say Raghu, it tastes just like it did back then.
I
How are you kid?
Iam good sir. Can I get you a cold drink?
No, thank you.
You know why I'm here, right?
Madhav sir felt sorry about your grandfather passing away.
But there's no place for sentiments in this field.
You know it very well.
Sir, please forgive me...I don’t have cash.
So, when will you return the cash?
J
Sir, 1 don’t know how to explain...
Meaning? What the hell does that even mean?
I y Aye. Aye
I
Sit down!
+
Who are you? This is our business!
wil
What kind of business is this, hitting a young boy?
Leave quietly, or else...
A
I'll get the cash from you one way or another. I'll be back!
I
ba
Yeah, get lost!
wz
What is this for?
Weapon.
Couldn't find anything smaller?
How about that Wada?
I was eating that Wada, so...
Leave this!
Hey Gautu, what's the matter? Who is he?
A I Ny I A) I I
Two years ago, before my parents passed away,
4 &
I
the hospital bills ran up to 15 lakhs.
Both of them were in the hospital for long,
i
...underwent great difficulties...
I
poor grandfather had to spend all his life-savings on hospital bills.
But that wasn't enough.
T-
Finally, he took a loan from Madhav.
T
He is a famous guy.
Why did he do so? He could have spoken to us, right?
A
You knew my grandfather, right?
: I
He doesn't like borrowing money at all.
D 4
In fact, he would advise against borrowing money from friends,
AY
He'd say if you can't repay them, then it ruins the friendship.
Even then...
Hey, let him finish first...continue, Gautham.
- -
So he borrowed 10 lakhs from Madhav,
on four percent interest,
)
...adding up to 20 lakhs now.
I
How much time do you have to repay him?
Within a month.
And what if you don't pay back?
I Lp
The cafe's documents are in his possession.
- I
Pandu uncle was mad or what?
Who gives original documents to borrow money?
A A
This place must be valued at 50 lakhs at least?
Not 50 lakhs.
It’s actually 70 lakhs.
&
Madhav has our documents.
Says it will pay off the loan.
struct a building here.
He wants to con
i
I don’t know what to do.
-
’ I
I don’t want to leave this place.
:
A A
I have grown up here,
I
even my father grew up here!
4 A
My grandfather loved this place.
I
hr
My grandfather loved this place
He took great pains to build this place.
All he wanted to do.
/
...was to make people eat tasty food.
I
I ¥ A A
He always said this place isn't just a hotel,
A 4
instead it should feel like
4 I
)
I
I feel bad for the kid.
1 I i
Children suffer for the sins of elders.
I -
Then what should have Uncle Pandu done? Ask his son to let him die in the hospital?
One does what he can, right?
a
©
It's not like that.
J
Couldn't he consider other options?
Look, there is no point talking about the past.
Now, can we help Gautu?
a 3 £
©   Q © ©
Let's talk about that.
see.
€
I'll ask my father if he can help.
What more can we do?
H c £
Why do you have to do that?
Let try to do something.
&
We have to do something.
I
Lets meet here tomorrow, share all our ideas. See where it goes.
Tomorrow again?
What is this?
I have got family.
I can't leave my family and sit here everyday.
So, we don’t have family... We are beggars.
I don’t talk to mad people
You keep quiet.
Raghu, just a few more days.
We can’t leave Gautham like this.
He will lose this hotel.
-
Pandu uncle was always like a master for us.
A
I
- n
He had helped us, guided us.
ne
It's time to repay him for his good deeds.
n
-
Raghu, don’t you wish his soul should rest in peace?
You're right...
But, we need to think practically.
Did I say I won't help him?
At best, we can pool in money and help him out.
What else can we do?
This is not just about money.
Right now Gautu needs our support.
He's like a family member.
I
But why waste time coming here everyday?
Let him leave...
4 -
Let’s be serious. How can we help him?
I
Even I am telling you seriously,
- 2
...we should try at least.
I
Let him go! Both of us will do something...
Selfish fellow.
Okay, I'll take your leave.
He is such a selfish fellow!
r x
It's okay. Let it be...we force anyone.
...let it be. Now, how should we help Gautu?
I wanted to have a word.
The thing is...
I spoke to Pandu uncle’s grandson, Gautam.
He's facing tough times.
Yes, Aasif.
They've fallen into the trap of a guy.
Now, it's upto us to do something.
That's the problem. They've got the cafe's documents, Kishor!
I
Now he has to repay almost 20 lakhs.
Very sad.
What if we help him out?
I feel sorry for his situation,
a but we don't have enough money to donate to strangers, do we?
Can we do anything about it?
He is not a stranger, Dad.
Pandu uncle was very close to us.
A
When I was in college, I used to regularly visit Kudla Café
I remember all those things. I didn’t forget.
Don’t you have any cash?
I pay you a salary, right? Do whatever you want with that money.
I don’t have money to spend for all these things.
Now, I am a bit busy.
I
Good night, Dad.
Pandu uncle.
R
You would've met him by now.
Take care of him till I get there myself.
AN
What happened dear, haven't slept yet?
—
p
I heard your conversation with Grandfather.
Overhearing elders is bad manners, my child.
I
) I
Don't know. I want to.
-
If mom was here,
she would have suggested what to do, right?
do as your heart says.
care about what others say.
Aren't you growing up fast? Talking like an old lady!
n
I
Brother, please don’t do this to me.
I'll return your money, anyhow.
I  Please, don't take my stuff.
Get out...move!
I've verified all the documents of this property.
N i
You got your chances. Get aside!
i
1 1 -
I
What's up? Having a good laugh?
a
Why is Raghu fuming? Joke's on him?
‘d i
He's become world famous in our area.
I
Why? What happened? What's the matter?
-
Raghu was swimming in the pond.
I
Bhaskar took his clothes and ran away!
Uncle, I had to go home in an under garment.
I
J
y
—
Everyone was staring at me, shocked.
I A
I never felt so embarrassed in my whole life......
I
Uncle, even you are laughing at me right?
»
There is no point telling my sad story....
To cover my body, I had to use coconut leaves.
On top of that, a dog started chasing me!
Are you guys my friends?
I I -
Better to not have friends at all!
I
Raghu, you should never say that.
-
I ——
In one’s life, friends are the most valuable gifts.
Did you understand?
p 4 £
We should always think before we speak.
a
!
I
Sometimes, God gives us exactly what we ask for.
Did you understand?
- I
Uncle, if he had to ask God for anything,
-
he would've asked for his clothes back.
I I I I
1)
Left...bend properly...right...
/
™
»
left...right...left...right...
J
I
Hey it’s not like that.
Then how? I find it difficult!
J I See me, I will show you
left...right...
) )
a
left...right...right...left...
A  Coming...coming.
left...alight...not light, rig
Let's spend some time thinking about how to get the money.
Scoot in.
A How come you're here? You said you won't come.
t come for you.
What? I didn”
So, what were you guys saying?
Gautu...How much cash do you have now?
I have got 3 lakhs.
You've got 3 lakhs...
What can we do for the rest?
’ I I 4 I can arrange for 1 lakh.
I have arranged for 1 lakh.
Oh...All poor people are done...
now let the boss speak....
Write 5 lakhs form my side...
I
What are you staring at?
Don't have to pay immediately, right? Later, right? I'll pay!
I
p I
I asked you to write.
I
We've to save him anyhow, right?
I don’t know how to thank you people.
)
& : 3
God blesses those who pick up the fallen.
A
I'll make sure that I repay all of you.
Then...Gautu’s 3 lakh...
I ail
aghu’s 1 lakh and 1 lakh from me...
AF
So, in total we have 10 lakhs.
4 I I
As for the remaining 10 lakhs...
£ I
Do we have any ideas?
u
Is brain working?
A I
What is this? You know we've to arrange 10 lakhs in a month!
/ Even a Bank won't give 10 lakh interest for a 10 lakhs deposit.
J
. 5
But I have got one super idea.
&
place is this?
This is my regular place. Why are you worried?
I don’t find it safe. Feels risky.
Life is full of risk!
Bhaskar, you know we're in trouble, right?
The troubled attract trouble.
But I have solutions. We need a good hand, a good weapon.
Weapon? Where is it?
Here! Get down.
Where is he taking us?
Where?
Come...Come...Come...
Windows are open man!
A The money's with him, right? Nothing to worry about.
I i
4 1,
Hey...Hey. Do you think this is Kindergarten?
I I
Anyone can come and join, huh? Who are these guys?
These people are with me.
So what, are they bigshots? Send them out.
-
Brother, we are his bodyguards.
— 8
Bodyguard?
You don’t need bodyguards to play cards.
I
— f
You need money.
I
If you've money then come and sit here.
You have it, right?
Of course!
A.
—
Then you come, let them sit there.
»
A
4 a
How much?
I
4 I
5 thousand for one.
Raghu give me 1 lakh.
Quickly.
Place cut.
Highest.
A N
Where will you sit?
1 will sit here.
I -
How much is the bet?
- "LL
5 thousand.
I
Why is he playing blind?
od I
10, seen.
10 seen...
J
Show...
:
I J
I think it’s enough, right?
I'll just tell him.
A
I
Bhaskar... I think it’s enough for today...
of
Don't be too ambitious.
a
Shouldn’t we be happy with what we have?
Are you mad?
This day'll never come back again.
It's my lucking lucky day! I'm not getting up!
I'll play safely, don’t worry...
Okay. Then we will be outside...
I'm suffocating here. You play safely.
A
I
Should we raise the stakes to 20 blind?
Twenty blind.
av a 2.
I didn’t have any hopes with Bhaskar,
But now I am very happy.
He is playing very safely, right?
Yes...Yes...
Another twenty.
Fifty.
Bhaskar has improved a lot now,
Doesn't play with a hothead like before.
Using his brain now.
This is a funny game, isn't it?
1 lakh becomes 4 lakhs overnight!
Let me call Gautu.
Yeah, okay
Hello, Gautu.
You don’t worry okay...
with God’s grace all our problems will be solved.
I
Had enough already?
One minute, I'll get more money.
Give me 1 lakh. Please...
el
What? You were making money?
Got over so soon?
Gambling is like that! You win some, you lose some.
a big round, give me more money.
I told you Bhaskar, don't be too ambitious.
Forget the past. My reputation's on the line.
I
Reputation? What about Commitment? This is Gautham’s money.
Are you not giving me the money?
No.
Just give me a lakh!
No, I won't!
Give me the money!
won't.
Please...I'll return it in double...
I know what to do, I have the confidence.
I
I will not give the money.
So you are not giving the money?
Get away.
J I
You guys just don't care.
I I I
Where are you going, turncoat?
Unlock the door.
Ask your mother to unlock it.
How will we go?
Take a boat!
What kind of mad man is he?
Will we get a boat at this time?
Thanks for dropping me, Daddy.
It's okay. When will your car be ready?
J
Daddy...please stop it.
What is this?
You act like a child sometimes.
A
Will you be coaching all your life or what?
Why shouldn’t I do it? I love my job
Why I do it? I love my job
Why do you need this job?
It’s not your future. Think about it.
See, didn’t I leave that job?
I'm not interested in leaving this job.
A I A
...take your water bottle
Raghu!
Coach, this is my father.
Hello.
Do you know my father?
a
Yes, he was my opposition team's coach.
Are you a player?
i During those days, he was the best Raider.
Oh really? Even Pooja is the best Raider in the team.
:
.
She's blessed with your tallent.
She has a good future in sports.
She just needs your support.
Come Pooja, let’s go...
Bye...I'll see you.
Bye...Dear.
A
Yesterday, it was a bit too much.
1) )
know.
I
I 4 "1
y I - A  / Gautham called me in the morning. the matter?
A 75 / You saw yesterday's madness, right? Maybe he doesn't need our help anymore.
7 NY
And what's Bhaskar's story today?
-
Hasn't been answering calls since morning.
¥
- ¥
) Let’s go to his house.
Even if he's mad, we need him, right?
Look how he's parked, Peter.
4  i
A
Ring the bell, there is a bell, right?
© ) 4
“ 4 i
1 I +
- 1 - 4
Bhaskar!
Ji
i I 7 a  ia
I a   - -
What's all this ruckus?
Did you sleep in the car, the whole night?
i
¥
Speak softly, others might hear it.
I
Yesterday you left us there itself...
Gautham had called, to meet up at the cafe.
A J
I don’t know why? Let's go and find out.
I A
Oh, parked it so far upfront, huh?
Ii
ffl
Oh, wasn't driving in the night?
Who is he?
fl
Even I don’t know who I came with at night.
3  S
The car is just short of kissing the porch.
E
Kabaddi!
I didn’t understand.
Yes, Kabaddi.
You serve in plates, right? Why are you serving me a newspaper?
“Getting the life partner of your choice”
“repaying the earlier debts”, “Bad luck following you around”.
What is this?
) 4 y
There's a Kabadi tournament within 25 days.
I
First time such a big tournament is being organized in Kudla.
A of
A
Many teams will come from different places. Do you know?
So what should we do?
A “ Federal Bank's Mangalore Branch will be sponsoring this tournament.
Kudla hasn't seen a tournament of this scale.
1)
But how is it connected with us arranging the money?
Check the wining amount.
A
Q
- Ne
For runners up it is 10 lakhs...
I
...and for winners it is 20 lakhs.
So, what are you saying?
- - So if we assemble a team,
train them and if they win...
...you think they'll just give 'us' the money?
ad
So what are you telling us?
Vd
Not assembling another team...
We play ourselves.
J
Two masalas, outside!
ES
Shut up you moron!
a
It's not necessary for us to win.
j ii.
Second prize is enough, too. Our problem will be solved.
What happened?
Why can’t you start playing again?
we can do it!
2 How is this possible? What are you saying?
a
I
We haven't played for thirty years!
I know it, Peter.
) A
don’t know why, but I feel we can do it.
J
What is this? Are we playing carrom?
J 2 Its Kabaddi. We can't play this game anytime we want.
I  He'll make promises and won't show up for the match,
Bhaskar, I know that...
I
A
l I have let you down. I feel for it,
but this is one great chance.
I Do you remember? How strong our team was?
Who is this?
Madhav...
I
What did you tell?
Madhav Sir...
Who are they? Your lawyers?
I don't like people messing with my property.
I
Even 'he' is my property.
5 a y wr
As revenge, I can cut off your hand, your leg or even your head.
I
I will not leave any one of you.
: I - I
Why work against the law, when the law is with you?
Right, Gautham?
I
You'll get your money in due time, Leave him alone till then.
Yes, that's important...
We are happy if we get our money...
After all, we're asking for it rightfully, aren't we?
Applying such high interest rates is fair or what?
His grandfather needed the money, not me.
Anyway, just wanted to remind you that, I'm still alive.
y I
Okay then, I'll take your leave.
Hey, listen.
I : I
You know their plan?
They'll win a Kabadi match!
Kabadi!
It might be good.
But, do you people have an idea about the game?
Gautham has trusted good people.
N"
Good, good.
Its all good.
N—
Kabadi is a very serious game.
I  I 1 I If you people join,
then it might provide some comedy.
Good time-pass.
I
I I
Okay. I will leave now. Won't come back again.
wi
It'll soon be mine...this place.
Come man.
We're definitely playing Kabadi!
7 ) / J L
We'll choke up that laughing devil!
Yes, you are right.
f
I trust you people.
I
Even grandpa used to say how strong your team was.
— MNT A po. I
It was Gautham. Look at us now.
What has happened? You people are still fit.
Look at me!
1 will play.
We don’t have any other option.
A
Do you have other options to make 10 lakhs in such a short period?
play man!
Playing is okay. But how do we win?
I
I strongly doubt you're a P.T teacher.
You must've joined as a janitor,
3 and since they had no choice, they put a whistle around your neck.
I
and fooled the kids.
A
We don’t have to win the tournament.
I I
We just have to reach the finals.
on
We have already arranged about 10 lakhs,
Runner-up is good, too.
No “If” no “But” Peter.
a Va
Why Peter, can’t we play?
3  I
Just think how well we used to play?
y I
We can surely do it. I guarantee it.
Yes, man, play.
Okay, I'll j ay, I'll join you guys
Wait...wait... what about rest of the players?
Will they join us?
see, call them
I doubt that they will come.
Most of them said they'll come.
God knows...
wait for some more time.
You people are here!
I
Aasif. I'm glad you guys came.
Can't we do at least this much for Pandu Uncle?
Sorry I couldn't make it to the funeral.
It’s okay. It's done, right?
I felt really bad. I won't miss anything now.
Come play.
4 4
1 I
4 3 It's been long
since my hands have touched the dirt.
We can see that with your stomach.
-
Kabadi...Kabadi...
Oh my God! It's difficult.
Difficult? Too difficult! Not as easy as we all thought!
5 Didn't I tell you? It’s been long since we've played!
J
/
But I didn't think we'll be out of touch so badly.
X N 2 I on! You were all a team!
. r
Right now, you're just not in form.
What farm? Chicken farm?
Not like that.
If you'll practice for some more time, then you'll find your form again.
Even if we practice, it's impossible for us to play like we used to.
y
Our team is missing one thing.
What is it?
»
Your grandfather...
I
4 1
He was the main reason we played so well.
" J.  I
Q
Without him, we can’t play like we used to.
:
n
Now what can we do?
£
I think we should't play.
"
You keep quiet man!
7 I
search for a new coach.
A a
Where will we find a coach at such a short notice?
I
There is one person
—
I am sorry.
k
I feel bad that, I can’t help you.
1 didn’t like your decision.
Don’t feel bad that I am saying this,
You're out of touch for 30 years now, I can't prepare you in 25 days.
A 4 But we do play well, Sir. Our old team has regrouped, Sir.
Raghu.
I know that you are a good player.
I always respected brother Pandu,
but now it is not possible
I By A L He says he can't then why're we arguing?
Sir, if you coach and us, we will definitely win.
Sir, if you coach and guide us, we will definitely win.
I know our tummies are bulging out,
but we'll definitely pull it in, Sir.
— A
I'm happy that you're playing,
but I wouldn't like to see you lose.
Zz
Anyhow...wish you all the best.
Thank you, Sir
When he wished us luck,
I didn't understand if he was encouraging us or the opposite.
A I
How about we make money thi
i  a
I
No, those things won't work.
i
Well, how are we going to play Kabaddi at this age?
¥
Why don't we organize our own tourna
i
i 4 -
0 1030
MEALS READY
Nothing seems to be working out.
I S08. MEALS READY
Gautham, what's there to eat?
I
Isn't he in a hurry!
One minute!
ha I I -
Okay. I've understood your situation.
a
1 will coach your team.
1 will coach you guys.
Something's happening in my stomach...
I
Why? Why I?
Because I'm a girl or too young
J J
We understand you have good intentions, but this is no child's play.
It is a difficult job.
You're just a little girl!
We will manage. You should go.
Brother Raghu,
what do I do for a living?
y
A
Kabadi coach, right?
ak 3 A
How does it matter whether a boy or a girl coaches you?
You don't have any other options.
Alright, let's do one practice session.
Little girl?
Hey, what is this? What?
Let's practice once. What have we got to lose?
Are you mad?
We are 45 years old!
Ba
J
And our coach will be a 25 year old girl?
Be
SN
People will have a good laugh at our expense.
ANTERMISSION
Come on guys.
Line up.
Good morning to all of you.
at’ 4
A
I am your new coach.
a J
It's been years since you've played,
r
so I'll test you first.
A
How old are you Mama?
N
Have you ever played Kabadi?
f
Please don’t take it lightly.
This is about our reputation.
HY
Girl, what's your experience?
x
These questions are not necess
I can prepare you, only if you listen to me.
i
¥
And no excuses.
4 I
So play. Come on,
J
I I go, Come on.
come, let's go, let’s go.
A I
‘da If
Let's see if we become Panthers or, remain to be Pandas.
F
NR
RY M ny
I  A
Take off your glasses.
No, I feel as if I am playing in shade.
wm
Can I start from tomorrow?
-
Brother Kishore, you go first.
In A
Brother Kishore...raid!
Brother Krishore...You have to raid.
y od
will catch him? He is a bit slow, isn't he?
f
Are you playing Kabadi or shaking hands?
¢ J
Stop, brother Kishore!
i a
Ld
Do you know what brother Bhaskar said about you?
What did he say?
I
He said you play like a little girl.
x I i
That you remind him of a pregnant cow.
:
4  +
Okay, I will give you the chance...
w
...to express your rage on the ground.
J w
will teach him...
Hey! Why is he carrying me? Has he lost
Hey Peter!
I A  i
You know what a mosquito is, right?
a4’
Mosquito...What?
Yes, they were calling you a mosquito.
It’s easy to kill a mosquito, it seems.
i
Were they calling me mosquito?
They're not aware what diseases they will get if the mosquito bites them.
I I
Now I'll show them the power of mosquito!
1 HA Ful I I -
L
god
4 4
That was the first day. We'll continue tomorrow.
Tomorrow sharp at 7 alright? Dismissed.
y
e said dismiss and left herself. Aren't we leaving?
© 2 2 ©
¢ y 2 y .
4 I
Let her go wherever she wants.
Are we coming tomorow?
¥
You're at least a P.T teacher, what do we do?
Your grandfather's loan is going to give us Arthritis.
is going
father's
£9 & N I
4 y Pp
Your grandfather's lo
to give us Arthritis.
is going
father's
c £
-
J
Your grandfather's loan is going to give us Arthritis.
4 —
I'll have to 'have' a bit today.
Why are you acting like a wet lotus?
Hey...easy.
/
y
First of all I'm getting a fever.
So? We are taking this pain killer liquid.
ji I
Whatever you say...
we got one coach...
we may not be fit,
but she has faith...that’s enough...
Yes that’s right...
she'll do something.
Very positive person!
B
I don’t have faith.
I guarantee we're going to lose.
-
I
talk negatively.
We've practice tomorrow. Lets see.
Whatever...I was very happy.
a After years, I stepped on the field.
Are you really a P.T teacher? I doubt it.
I y
/
But I'm so nostalgic right now...
I've missed lot of things, Peter.
Brother Raghu...where are you?
I
Gautham?
We've been waiting to start practice!
Okay...okay...coming.
How long you will take?
Soon. Right now!
Guys, get up!
a
Get off me...
Let's go, quickly. Let's go!
Bhaskar...
Get up...get up...
Let's go...let's go...let's go.
A a ¥
Still drunk and he says let's go...
)
But does he know where we've to go? Do you know?!
Wherever man.
I
So then, how was it last night?
e enjoy?
I A you peopl
Di
a
4 I
What was there to drink?
I I bt To drink? We blast!
had a
A 4 I
3 of us finished 2 bottles completely.
I
god...
Oh my god...
J I
You guys are quite something, aren't you?
/ H
each one of you must've had three quarters of a bottle, right?
)
Three quarters?
I had a full bottle, these two shared one. even finished the last 60 ml.
I -
I » Fars A
So, you have the highest capacity in the group, right?
I My father had more capacity... I am...not so much...
3 4
Wow...then it’s decided.
d A
You can run 10 rounds,
» A,
while they share 5 rounds each...
2 ny Are you serious?
Didn't you say you have the highest capacity in the group?
A
& A
I §
Isn't there a difference in running and drinking?
A
/ 3 )) y 4
When I talk, you don't talk. Understood?
H x
v ¥
Good...
I
If you want to play, then show some passion. Otherwise, don't waste my time.
A Start forget about it.
3 12
I 3
5 2
We're serious. Won't happen again. This was all his fault.
Good
...get ready.
L a
Brother Bhaskar...10 rounds, rest of you, 5 rounds...come on.
4 4 Do we also need to run 5 rounds?
t you with them last night?
Why? Weren
Okay, he wasn't.
Okay.
I
Doesn't matter, you still get 5 rounds.
Come on.
1 Hi
you waiting
What are you waiting for?
K
Get ready...Go.
I i
Me and my big mouth!
I I
k
Me and my big mouth!
u're not done yet
A
Enough for today. Let's regroup tomorrow.
r  i
Tomorrow 7 AM means sharp 7 AM.
:
4 3
continue later...
3 A
Someone inform the dead body as well.
RS A
Dead Body?
“
Bye, Pooja.
A :
Admit me in a hospital.
Govinda...Govinda.
r
Oh my god!
Daddy,
May I ask you something?
Sure.
I I
Why did you stop playing thirty years ago?
It’s an old story dear, leave it.
Was it because of Grandpa?
- I
It’s not that simple. Let it go.
He asked you to stop, right?
" All y
He didn’t like it.
I'd lose track of time...
chanting 'Kabadi', 'Kabadi' all day.
He didn't appreciate it.
But you liked to play, right Daddy?
I loved it very much,
I'd played State level,
I would've got National Level.
Then why didn’t you play?
You're just a little girl, who won't understand.
-
Then make me understand daddy.
But it's good I stopped.
I met your mother,
I married her, you were born.
I could improve your grandfather's business.
Look how happy we are now.
It was tough, when I was your age.
But you could've met mom even if you played.
A
I would've happened too.
i
Our life wouldn't have been posh, but we'd be happy.
It’s late dear.
-
Go to your room and sleep.
Good night, Daddy.
BE
Your daughter has many questions.
I don’t know how to answer them.
/
everyone's on time.
I » I
r I  00
T y I
So, shall we begin?
/
Let’s do some warm-up exercises and strengthen your old muscles.
na
Alright...so everybody...
bend down and touch your feet...
I
1 che 2 A Touch your feet properly...
) I a. I
Brother Bhaskar, you've to come back up as well.
ke it down here.
I'll come up in my own time.
v
Want to run 10 rounds today, to up!
Want to run 10 rounds today, too? Come up!
- 4 - -
That's why I always say...
A you should always keep your body fit like me,
I I
not drink every evening.
I Buzz off!
»
A I
Stomach's like a tyre, calls himself fit!
2 J
y
You are a P.T teacher, right?
a
Nowadays even I'm doubting it.
I 7  I
i
Brother Bhaskar, will you listen to me? Come up!
© § 4
&
N X
Stretch...go all the way down.
if I y
Brother Bhaskar...stop.
Your grandfather killed us.
As you all know,
main thing in Kabadi is breathing.
When you are raiding you need to say Kabadi...Kabadi...at least for 30 seconds.
- I
at players practice for years to achieve that.
- It's been 3
0 years since you've played. You can’t do it.
The tournament's a few days away...
so we'll have to try a short cut method...
I
Short cut method means?
Whose head is this?
A a
I didn’t know we'll have to do all this.
2 5 8
Are you really a P.T. teacher?
© »
Poor children.
»
a, everyone doesn’t have to raid, right?
Then why're you testing our breathing limits?
-
Ours isn't a professional team...
F 4
+
anyone might get a chance to raid.
Wh
Now get inside the water...
e E &
Don’t get out until I tell you to.
Cc
& Any doubts?
€
¢ -   re
Why do we need this test? Sink!
Are you people tired?
I
I was just thinking.
We should keep a name for our team, right?
£
How about Kudla Warriors?
, .
r
Sounds like a herd of goats.
a
AS 4
asked for a good name.
A ?
"Kudla Warriors"!
/
Do you know the meaning of
What?
J
No salt, no assault.
Suggest something else.
How about
AA
It's scary for all the wrong reasons.
I I
A
y If you guys don’t mind, I've an excellent name for our team.
What is it?
JB
May I suggest a name?
wi ¥
It's Deadly Seven.
“Mamu’s Boys”
Super name.
Its late. Shall we leave?
go...let’s go. Come.
Come Bhaskar. go.
You people carry on. I'll play water sports for a while.
§
Bhaskar’s Sports team!
Go in your undies now.
i 4
. I 4
You hide then I seek. I hide then you seek...this is life.
will teach you.
Good evening.
I'm trying to do body building.
You embarrass me?
Thank God, they've left the keys!
- 2 I
My body feels tight. From 1 and half, it's reaching 4 packs now.
I am feeling relaxed.
I — How did I know that this is a lu home?
a lunch home?
Oh... they're in our spot.
Oh, Gauthu!
I
There is no place to sit.
di
Ni
I
Pandu Uncle would've been happy today.
No need to play the match now. Business seems good.
Oh my God! She's killed me...I'm dead.
(  Oh my God,
Why did you do this?
You don’t even know to drive a car?
Who me? Ask him...
He came in front of my car.
Please get me down from the ambulance...Please!
Ask your people to be more careful.
Yes...Yes...It's my mistake itself.
Till date, I thought footpath was meant for pedestrians.
Today I came to know...
I'm mad, that I was walking on the footpath.
s not this mistake.
It
Oh, senior citizen,
I'm sorry if you're hurt,
but I blew the horn.
I didn’t hear it.
Take that cotton out of your ears,
then you'll hear it.
What if something would've gone wrong?
Is this how you talk to your coach?
What did you say?
Coach?
Mine?
You are my coach at the Kabadi ground. Not here!
Please tell her.
It okay...Leave it.
No one's hurt, right?
He's not dead! Still fresh!
Why worry?
She's our coach...respect her!
We need money, right?
Tonight...
there's a local tournament.
J
I've made your entry...
A
Are we ready for it now?
Let's see.
I  I
We'll find out tonight.
-
Come on.
When I was with Pandu Uncle... people would respect me...
now I am treated like rubbish!
I
Literally killed me!
ad
Oh my God!
DY
MEALS REA
- I We thank all the sports fans attending this program.
And the good news is,
Madhav Sir, owner of Urwa Kings, is also present today.
We heartily welcome him.
I
What is Madhav doing here?
And strong favourites, the undefeatable,
Urwa Kings are here.
They've consistently won the trophy for 3 years.
Truly, a champion side.
Against them, a new team, Mamu'’s Boys.
i ) Each player is exemplary, that's why they're so consistent.
Oh, this is team!
-
I -
I
Their self confidence, game spirit and technique...
of Tig f !
makes Urwa Kings the strongest team.
Funny feeling in the stomach again.
4 J
No problem. Big ground. Ambulance can come in.
I I - - a I Looking at the Urwa Kings team, Boys seem nervous.
I /  a
Why did we get his team?
J
A I
The nervousness showing on their faces...
y  I
Be strong and don’t be scared.
Referee's on the ground.
Both captains, come forward.
I
———
He's asked both captains to step up.
i
Where're you going? You're not the captain.
I
- 3
a
Call for Boys.
Heads...
Okay, toss is won by Urwa Kings!
We lost the toss, too.
We don’t even have a uniform.
Seeing Urwa Kings, Mamu'’s Boys are losing their confidence...
-
and they've lost the toss, too.
Urwa Kings first raid is made by Danny...
38 /
We should see how Mamu’s Boys will defend...
A J 7
Touched the first ma d the third man!
A
Two points in the first raid for Urwa Kings.
Id 2 £
Go. You are out, right?
if plan A fails REME MBER
see how Boys will play.
I'll go, I'll go.
From Boys, captain Raghu has come to raid.
I
Urwa Kings are defending in 2, 1, 2 formation.
f y
Raghu is finding it difficult ...
» A I but, even he has touched the third and scores 1 point.
:
So for Boys team, first man will get in.
So for Mamu’s Boys team, first man will get in.
Urwa Kings' Yadhav has got in now.
Urwa Kings has scored one point again.
/ -
Was I supposed to get a dream that he will come so fast?
Mamu’s Boys' player' Raghu, raids again.
But unfortunately he loses.
I "
For Urwa Kings total 4 points.
LUN
- -
We hope that he is not hurt.
Now from Urwa Kings, its turn to raid.
Now from Urwa Kings, its Vijayannada’s turn to raid.
) I
he kicks...they lunge...
and he's across!
J I gal
Urwa Kings scores 3 points.
I
Raider safe.
3 points to Urwa Kings.
L
(
Everyone else is out!
r
This chilled out player se to have cold feet.
Come on brother Bhaskar.
Looks like he'll play well may be he'll score one or two points.
Enou gh! Enough! Enough! !
Just put me down right there. Thank You.
As Boys are all out...
Urwa Kings get 2 extra points
-
so before changing sides,
Boys get one more shot to defend their side.
Urwa Kings have won this match effortlessly.
4 »
Crushing Mamu's Boys with a difference of 23 points,
just as we expected.
J  AL
—
I tell you we play Kabadi at this age?
You should've given me the money. would've doubled it!
©   o
§
Just keep quiet Bhaskar, don’t keep irritating!
Just keep quiet don’t keep irritatin
Good job guys.
What good job?
Good job, it seems!
Now you know how it feels to lose.
Next, we will learn how to win.
See you at practice.
Bhaskar, I can’t see! My eyes, my eyes!
How can you, if they turned off the lights, Peter!
-
How much? 5 lakhs?
Yes, yes...
I 4 I
5 Lakhs...
A I
can you please arrange it somehow?
r a I'm in great difficulty. It’s a matter of my reputation.
What difficulty? I don't have that much.
-
Or else...at least 3 lakhs?
I can give you the money,
— T 4 but who'll run behind you to recover that money?
I'm requesting you...
A
-
When my wife returns...
A
I'll sell the house with her permission.
A Why'll you sell the house? You wear so much gold.
-
only to keep up an image.
I
It's not gold.
If you wear fake gold,
how are you going to pay me back?
Hang up!
ry
v
Adi
I don't have money for beggers.
- 4
a
e Tourname Must have drank last night.
what do you say we do now?
Should we wait or start?
- Let's start. Why should we wait?
Yes, get up. Come on...Let’s go.
I 3
I
Where has Bhaskar died today?
x 3
Let it be,
»
I A
go and look for him.
I B i
Go ahead.
Bye, Gautham.
I i I
kay. Okay.
»
m N 2 2 4
What happened?
Car isn't starting?
Come...
sit on my bike.
I'll drop you.
m .2 N 2 2 4
—
m 2 2 4
m N 2 a 4
What happened?
m 2 2 4
'I
I  I
i
Bike isn't starting?
m nN hy 3 a 4
His car's here.
Bhaskar...Is he not there?
He isn't in the car.
Door's open!
Hey...Bhaskar!
Why is he on the floor?
Bhaskar...Bhaskar... What happened, Bhaskar?
He's finding it difficult to breathe...
Peter, take him to the hospital.
— ) I I
A - I  I :
Oh, by the way it's acute alcohol poisoning.
There's no problem, right?
No problem.
/ f
Al
Generally, depression leads to
an alcohol
— I -
I've asked him to take extra care. Okay?
—/
» I J Okay. okay.
Our Bhaskar?
-
He usually gets others depressed.
JA
That we can’t tell Peter.
What we see may not be the truth, right?
- I've felt he is upset about something.
He tell us...that’s it!
You know him, right?
He won't disclose anything to anyone.
4 .
Come, see.
/ i I - y
I I  Zi
don’t know what
to me last night?
We were scared...
I
seeing you like that...
What is the matter?
Is there any tension?
No problem, right?
What kind of questions are you asking?
-
Can't you see this pipe?
Are they joking with all these things?
Stop being silly...
I didn’t mean it like that.
I
Do you have any other tensions...
in your family life?
Share it with us.
Nothing as such...
No worries... 'm very happy!
What is this Bhaskar?
We are your friends.
We've to finish what we've started, Bhaskar.
Don't leave us in between.
I
I'm with you guys.
If you're with us, then quit drinking.
You're right.
I'm creating a big mess.
Now just wait.
By the time the match gets over,
I won't even touch alcohol.
By any means.
Z
We can atleast do this much for Pandu Uncle, Bhaskar.
ay 1 of the Tournament
Day 1 of the Tourna
I
I I FEDERAL BANK FEDERAL BANK I" I FEDERAL BANK I I
Welcome to the Federal Bank Kabadi Tournament, organised by Dakshina Kannada district amateur Kabadi association.
I FEDERAL BANK
I
2 2 J i
H 5
16 Teams will take part in this tournament,
vs
H I &
with 8 teams in each group.
- BF I BOOLIYA FRIENDS 00
2 teams with the highest wins in their group, will play the finals tomorrow.
J Today's first match will be Booliya Friends v/s Boys.
We haven't seen this much crowd even in state tournaments.
After all, the prize money for winners is '20
And for runner’s up its '10
Referee has called captains of both the teams.
Now referee will flip the coin.
Mamu’s Boys win the toss.
- -
Mamu’s Boys will raid first.
we 4
/
From Boys te: their captain will be raiding first.
I I
Easily done and Mamu's Boys score 1 point.
Yk
—
Now first raid from Booliya friends.
I 1
4 He's crossed the bonus line...
Mamu’s Boys had an easy chance to catch him.
I
Boys get one more point.
Now from Boys...
another raider...
/
—
The way Booliya friends are play
it seems that they will gain a point.
- -
a Mamu’s Boys have not just gained one, but two points.
A LA 4
So, in total they have 4 points.
N I -
Now Booliya team's raider...
-
needs to be careful, since they haven't scored yet.
J ¢
Hey Raghu...catch his leg!
Good catch by Mamu's Boys' first man!
Including this one, they've 5 points in all.
z
:
Can't get enough of Mamu's Boys.
-
These oldies are giving young Booliya Friends a good fight.
I
Now only 2 players left in Booliya Friends...
I I
He touches both players and crosses the line easily!
I YQUR PERFE
Booliya Friends are all out now.
I With the bonus points, Boys' total is 9 points.
A 2 / I
»
Look at that, one more point!
Third raid from Boys.
ww
KK I KESARI KODIKER
Urwa Kings have qualified for tomorrow's final match.
— KK I KESARI KODIKERE I 27
Boys v/s Kesari Kodikere game has been a draw.
/
This game has come to an interesting point, rarely have we witnessed something like this!
Now it's upto the 'golden raid".
There's only one raid...
3 only if the raider scores a point, will they proceed to the finals.
Referee flips the coin.
Toss won by Boys.
I
Let's see how he gets the point.
A Bhaskar, we fully trust you. You'll surely get the point.
I We'll come to know their fate just within 30 seconds.
Bhaskar, 1 point means 10 lakhs.
4 We'll save Kudla Café back. It's in your hands.
Bhaskar, be steady, You can do it!
Bhaskar, we won! We've won Kudla Café!
Thank you brother Bhaskar. Thank you!
After a cliffhanger, Mamu's Boys have won by just 'one' point.
yo
Tomorrow's finals will be Boys v/s Urwa Kings.
I
We thank the audience for being here.
I y
We would need your support for the finals as well.
I y »
N
Cheers! Cheers!
-
I
Cheers to our coach Sanjana!
A, J
of
Where were you?
Nowhere Dad. We just went out.
- If we win its good. If we lose its okay. We've already saved Kudla Café.
Come, have breakfast.
Congrats, son...
you've reached finals it seems.
-
This is a small city...
3 What did you think? I wont come to know?
I i ¢
be I  S
This is what you've been upto?
You lied to me again!
Just for that stupid game.
You've taught your daughter well...
I
i I —
how to lie to your parents.
I I
! I 4
I i I
I'll never lie to my father.
Pooja!
What did you say?
I
Just what you heard...
I I I
that I won't lie to my father.
I
That's what I have learnt from him.
You only see!
This is how you brought her up!
Is this the way she talks to her grandfather?
A
Just have your breakfast...
didn’t I ask you not to poke your nose when elders are talking?
A
al I can’t bear it when you get scolded unnecessarily.
Grandpa,
I'll never lie to my father, because...
-
he never gave me that opportunity.
He used to listen to whatever I said,
then he used to guide me,
ma
and never controlled me.
If you want to be a good father,
Ll
Don't you understand?!
1&8
I  I
How many times do I've to tell you?
A
Is that the way you talk to your grandfather?
I I L z N
I I I
everyone's waiting at the ground.
Today's the final match. We be late.
So, you're going to play today?
Yes, Dad.
Today, I'll play.
Dad, I am a good son,
m I love my daughter. I love you, too.
I 4
I love my life, too.
—— Just because I skipped that day, I've been regretful for 30 years.
With God's grace, I've got a second chance.
I'll not repeat the same mistake, Dad.
If I do, who knows if I'll get another 30 years to regret.
A
If it's possible, please do come.
fx 4
It's not that bad a game.
I That day you asked us to write 5 lakhs. Now you're saying you don’t have it!
©  £
I
What happened? Tell me!
A
Ask this dog right here!
Will someone explain clearly?
He doesn’t have the cash, Raghu...
Which money?
The money which he said he'll give.
Now he doesn’t have the money, it seems.
“
Everything's gone to waste!
-
Don’t call it a waste, Peter.
What's the problem in it?
, Raghu?
Are you mad
Tomorrow, we are just getting 10 lakhs.
He said that he will give 6 lakhs, right?
5 lakhs to give and 1 lakh which he used for gambling.
¢
okay.
Is it right? Now we have 4 lakhs, right?
For 6 lakhs, what are we going to do?
You fooled us!
Yes, I've fooled you.
I don’t have the money...
3 4
I never had the money.
It's been 3 months that my wife and son have left.
a
was a partner for a new bus service,
f
but because of drinking habits, they threw me out of the partnership.
There is no one for me. I'm all alone.
I don't have the money, Raghu.
on’t have money.
Id
)
What's the point of saying these things now?
Why didn't you tell us before?
I didn’t want to spoil the hopes you had with me.
But, now I can’t prove myself.
Leave it!
Everything's over now.
"Ric
Our opposition in the finals is Madhav's team.
You know how we lost to them earlier, right?
Everything is over.
We've done our best, but what to do?
Are you people finished? Is it over?
Since I've come here, you people have been speaking nonsense,
saying that we'll lose the game.
Peter, we will win...
we have to win this!
Then you only go and play.
will not come.
I can’t take another beating from them.
He's right, Raghu.
We can’t beat them in the match.
I 4 4 If we take a step back, then we'll lose the opportunity to win.
Whatever happens...
I'll definitely play.
I'll play today evening.
If we lose, we lose.
1 ¥
Once when I skipped the match, I had to regret for 30 long years.
y
This time, I'll not allow it.
/
IN
What if that day Bhaskar would have forgiven me...
...would we've been away for so long?
peat his mistake.
won't re
I won't repeat his mistake.
That's why, I'm not mad at him.
A
We live happily with negative thoughts, Peter.
i —
Today we are playing not just for the sake of Café
there is something more than that.
It is upto you people whether you're coming or not.
by 4 I'll not play.
can doit!
I'll play tonight.
A
, we lose.
If we lose
Once when I skipped the match, I had to regret for 30 long years.
This time I won't allow it.
Brother Raghu...
They may not come,
not get ashamed like this.
y ( KC
Let's go and tell the referee.
KC I
You've accepted your loss too soon!
Look over there...
I knew that you people will definitely come.
Aasif. Kishore.
Yes, Raghu.
You were right.
Let's finish what we've started.
on
Where is Bhaskar?
Didn’t he come here?
We didn’t meet him.
ot at home either.
He is n
We thought that he might 've come here.
- A 1
We play with 6 players. Its better that we leave.
A I
y
Federal Bank final match will begin in few moments.
4 4 I Inaugral lamps have been lit.
I 5
Everyone is requested to occupy their places on the ground.
a The most awaited final match will begin in few more minutes.
I & Pad
I know someone...
A
He said that he'll help you guys.
Can I join you boys?
A
Thank you, thank you.
-
Let's play well.
Okay...
/  Come on boys... Come on! do it!
Both the teams, get in.
N )
Toss won by Mamu’s Boys.
—— -
I
Mamu’s Boys have won the toss and selected the court.
i
So, Urwa Kings will raid first.
FEDERAL BANK R PERFECT BANKING PARTNER
G PARTNER A
Final match has begun.
BAN
PARTNER
First raid by Urwa Kings' captain, Danny.
vi
Raider has won the first point.
a “ A
-
Now, Mamu’s Boys will do their first raid.
A Boys' captain has taken a super dive and they get 2 points.
Urwa Kings 1 point. Boys 2 points.
I I Urwa Kings 1 point. Mamu’s Boys 2 points.
-J
I ar
Urwa kings' strong raider Ravi has stepped in...
-
Mamu's Boys left corner's first man's effort has failed.
i If
Boys unable to show yesterday's spirit.
A 4 y
ven if you're scared, you should go.
because the fault is all yours.
I I
-
Even if you drink, gamble...
't marry a coward.
But, I know I didn
But now if you don’t go to play,
I
you will be a coward.
I I
v
- I
What is wrong with you?
Where has your spirit gone?
-
We've reached the finals, but you're still not playing your real game.
What Gautham?
/
What is going on in your brains?
Our defense has become too weak!
I don’t care what you do?
€
Pull up your socks and get going.
Good-looking trophy, right?
This Trophy will be mine,
the café will be mine, too.
It's surprising that you oldies made it this far.
Admirable.
But it ends here, understood?
Okay then,
If you guys are so keen to get ashamed, then I hope you die of the embarrassment.
A  -“
- It's not enough if you just have strength in your body,
you need some muscles up here too.
I
BANK 4 I
Body is about to collapse...
L
but still you people are struggling.
There are many in the world who have no strength,
but make a livelihood.
Clapping up on stage is not enough.
Get down, then you'll know who we are.
Raghu,
/
I'm sorry I'm late.
4 44 If want to play in your team, will you allow me to play?
I've promised my wife that I won't cry.
- Your wife has come?
Where is she?
at least for Kudla Café, we have to win this match!
1 4
Give me your jersey.
I
What are you staring at?
Are you going to play?
Do what I say!
Everything will be alright.
h
a
I . After the half time,
Bhaskar has rejoined the
T
ed the Mamu
s
x
and Urwa Kings' owner Madhav has also joined the team.
First raid after half time is from Bhaskar.
2 4 w
and he's crossed the line!
I
...and he's crossed the line!
It’s a good start for Mamu’s Boys in the second half.
Now, Urwa Kings will raid.
An amazing attempt!
o!
N They've taken him down.
I Unbelievable sight, as the strong Danny, captain of Urwa Kings, is tackled by Mamu's Boys.
Total score of Boys is 10 and Urwa Kings is 25.
aiding.
Boys' smart player is r:
5,
,
A Beautiful play and Boys get 2 points.
&
Now the Urwa Kings' owner Madhav is going for his first raid.
Till now, I haven't seen a team owner playing.
This is a special game.
Go man...
a
What is this? Fight!
ic  r ©
o  © Qo  I 5 £  3 1
Definitely, he'll get the green card.
Urwa Kings' Madhav gets a green card.
A
i 4
If he repeats it, a then Madhav might get a Yellow card.
He'll also get a 2 minute suspension.
Now it’s the raid from Boys.
Escaping from Avinash’s strength, he has crossed the line.
il
Mamu’s Boys get 2 points.
3 ! 3  2 4 ¥
Last player, Urwa Kings' Madhav is raiding.
ZY ) I
( A
Successful tackle by the second man.
Urwa Kings are all out!
M
Boys are playing really well in the second half.
They have shaken up a strong team like Urwa Kings.
A
Time out to Urwa Kings
AT
I
Total score is 26 Urwa Kings and 17 Boys.
I ) I
EENED AI D
Last 3 minutes to go...
Al
4 A
EDERAL BANK
DUR PERFECT BANKING PA
G PARTNER
FEDERAL BANK I PARTNER OUR PERFECT BANKING PA
I EDERAL BANK
i
Come on boys, come on!
A I a Oh, wow they've got the point! Now both the teams are equal.
AMU’S BOYS
With 30 seconds left, both the teams have got 33 points each.
i
Only 1 raid is left.
Mamu’s Boys have played really well in the second half.
‘a Al
I In few more minutes, we'll come to know who'll win the Federal Bank Tournament.
I In this raid if Madhav gets 1 point,
if Boys catch him, then they will definitely win the game.
TE   I
i
Federal Bank Kabadi Tournament 2015 winners are,
I
Boys!
I :
Give us the records...
Give him the cash.
Take your cash,
count it properly.
From today onwards, your business with this Café and Gautham is done.
Dare we see you around him ever again!
After all, you know us, right?
We know how to make you kiss the dirt and chuck you out as well.
Cet up...Go out...
y
Here Gautham, your records...
What next?
Next?
State Level Kabadi championship is coming soon.
TOE Kudla Sai Krishna
Naveen D. Padil
kao TOE
Kao Ravoor Kudla Sai Krishna
Naveen D. Padil
Sai “
Aksshay Mehta