or characters was purely coincidental.
I 4
I
M
Presents
y
Your job will B one only if you give Rs. 1,50,000 by tomorrow 3 P.M.
o 2 2    a o S 2 o o 3 23 o
Your job
Itis 5-10K. It is it possible for you?
? 3  o  o a o o
10K. It is Rs.
ot 5-
o B o © S c S © o  3
™ . e - - - - - -
Shall I put four consignments this we
Shall I put four this
-
I have to bear the loss if I listen
S'rqr
But, can you please give with Tlh e is some
some emergencys &
No But, can you please
&
A No But, can you please give soige advance with
IS some
is some emergency.
No But, can you please give with this X
AR
(Background voice) I “Your job will be done only if you give Rs. 1, 50 000 by tomorrow”
N‘
Cam you see? Are you blmd? Get lost. I
(Background voice) job will be done give Rs. 1,50,000 by tomoM
(Background voice) jol Il be done only if you give Rs. by tomorrow”
i “Your job will be done only if Rs. 1,50,000 by tomorrow”
(Background voice) “Your job will be if you give Rs. 1,50,000 by tomo
There & I want fou
r
xes immediately. Can N
in I want boxes
-
There home. I want boxes Vo
/ I I  here is & my home. I four boxes immediately. Ga supply?
gram in my home. I want four boxes immediately. Can you supply?
A
a program in my home. I want four boxes ImmedIateIy Canjyou § I ¥
is in I want boxes Can
J
is alprogram in home I want boxes immediately. C.
Now you give one bex for will give the full advance fo
rest of the order.
will gIve yﬁl the full advane he order.
-
Now you give one box for sam le.
/ / Thank you sir. Please take this box...
. ‘ /
4 /
hank you sir. Please take this box:..
Thenk you take this
you Plezse talke this
which you asked for.
ere it?
Wi
But when you
£
ere su posed it?
- )  hat is the -
I
ease doctor... Save my moth€ e no one else except her. Please...
,, doctor... Save my mother I
e except her. Please...
ave my mother. I have no one else except her. Please...
—
- Ok don’t cry. Come, let’s see your mother.
A
, worry. is done. Your mother is safe now.
There are many, money.
I
But these people struggle day &/
But these people struggle day S
righteous
But thes ’ ) o.earn it in righteous way.
Diseases don’t spare rich and Same thing happened with his
A
Diseases don’t spare rich and poo
g
Diseases don’t spare rich thing happe mother.
Diseases poor. S ing I ‘ ) &
f
n earn money, only if you are
ey is not everyti‘n You cg I
4 is notve only if you are aljve.  )
B
I I happy I ith what I have
a doctor
be pickles:
g0 to
to
els,
ill be served with picl
ckles.
y
I am not but the
is great:
but the ha
s saved a life is great.
a  not great, but t
he pickle which has saved a life is great.